gaspowered.com 2009-02-09

# Gas Powered Games: Privacy Policy

| 

| |   

Last updated: September 2nd, 2008

**OUR PRIVACY COMMITMENT**

Gas Powered Games respects the privacy rights of our online visitors and recognizes the importance of protecting all information that you may choose to share with us.

This Privacy Statement and the certification seal shown on this page confirms that Gas Powered Games is a valid member in [ESRB's Privacy Online Program](http://www.esrb.org/privacy.asp). ESRB's Privacy Online Program is designed to alleviate consumers' privacy concerns by ensuring a website's information disclosure practices are responsible and appropriate.

### TABLE OF CONTENTS

  1. What information does this Privacy Statement cover?
  2. What types of personally identifiable information do we collect about our guests?
  3. How is your personally identifiable information used and shared?
  4. What choices do you have about the collection, use, and sharing of your personally identifiable information?
  5. What kinds of security measures do we take to safeguard your personally identifiable information?
  6. How can you update your personal information and profile?
  7. How can you ask questions, or send us comments, about this Privacy Policy?
  8. How will you know if we amend this Privacy Policy?

| 

### Q1

| 

**What information does this Privacy Statement cover?**  
  
---|---  
  
### A1

| 

This Privacy Policy applies only to personally identifiable information ("personal information") collected on the Websites where this Privacy Policy is posted, and does not apply to any other information collected by Gas Powered Games through any other means. 

This Privacy Policy applies to use and sharing of personal information collected on and after the date that this Privacy Policy is posted.

This Privacy Statement applies to the following website:

www.gaspowered.com

Finally, the terms of this Privacy Policy are subject to all applicable laws.

top  
  
### Q2

| 

**What types of personally identifiable information do we collect about our guests?**  
  
---|---  
  
### A2

| 

We collect several types of personally identifiable information about our guests. Personal information is information that identifies you and may be used to contact you.

### Children

We don't knowingly collect any personal information from children 13 and younger.

### Information You Provide to Us

All of the personal information we receive comes directly from our adult guests. We collect personal information from our guests to:

  1. Register for our website
  2. Newsletter subscription
  3. Message boards and chat rooms
  4. "Tell-a-friend" or "Email this page" features
  5. Polls, surveys, or questionnaires
  6. Demo downloads
  7. Technical support

Typically, this information includes name, email address, telephone number, ICQ, AIM, and MSN contact information. Additionally, we may also collect other types of non-personal information (known as demographic information) such as your age, date of birth, or hobbies and interests.

We don't require personal information to access our site. However, if you prefer not to disclose personal information, you will not be able to enjoy certain features of our site.

Whatever the purpose may be, we will only collect information to the extent reasonably necessary to fulfill your requests and our legitimate business objectives.

### Business Information

For practical reasons, we treat personal information submitted to us in a business capacity (like job inquiries) different from information we receive in a non-business capacity. Personal information submitted to us in a business capacity may be shared with third parties, depending on the nature of the inquiry.

### Information Collected Through Technology

We collect information through technology to make our sites more interesting and useful to you. For example, when you come to one of our sites, we collect your IP address. An IP address is often associated with the portal through which you enter the Internet, like your ISP (Internet service provider), your company, or your university. Standing alone, your IP address is not personally identifiable. At times, we also use IP addresses to collect information regarding the frequency with which our guests visit various parts of our sites. We may combine this information with personally identifiable information.

### Cookies

Our Websites also use cookies. Cookies are pieces of information that a Website sends to your computer while you are viewing the Website. We and other companies use cookies for a variety of purposes. For example, when you return to one of our sites after logging in, cookies provide information to the site so that the site will remember who you are. 

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Netscape Navigator or Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn cookies off, you won't have access to many features that make your web experience smoother, like the features mentioned above, and some of our services may not function properly. 

Finally, once you've clicked on a hyperlink and have left our Websites, our Privacy Policy no longer applies and you must read the privacy policy of the owners to see how your personal information will be handled on their site.

top  
  
### Q3

| 

**How is your personally identifiable information used and shared?**  
  
---|---  
  
### A3

| 

As described in detail below, we do not disclose your personal information to third parties.

### Partners

We don't disclose your personal information to our partners. However, we may share aggregate consumer data - which does not contain any personal information - with our partners.

We may also use your personal information for other purposes such as "Operational Uses." For example, we may use your information to send you administrative communications either about your account with us or about features of our Websites, including any future changes to this Privacy Policy.

Finally, we may take your personally identifiable information and make it non-personally identifiable, either by combining it with information about other individuals (aggregating your information with information about other individuals), or by removing characteristics (such as your name) that make the information personally identifiable to you (de-personalizing your information). Given the nature of this information, no restrictions apply under this Privacy Policy on our right to aggregate or de-personalize your personal information, and we may use and share in any way with third parties the resulting non-personally identifiable information.

### Purchase or Sale of Businesses

From time to time, we may purchase a business or sell one or more of our businesses and your personally identifiable information may be transferred as a part of the purchase or sale. If we purchase a business, the personally identifiable information received with that business would be treated in accordance with this Privacy Policy, if it is practicable and permissible to do so. If we sell a business, we will include provisions in the selling contract requiring the purchaser to treat your personally identifiable information in the same manner required by this Privacy Policy (including any amendments to this Privacy Policy), if it is practicable and permissible to do so. The provisions of this paragraph will also apply if we are sold as part of bankruptcy proceedings.

Disclosures Required By Law and Disclosures to Help Protect the Security and Safety of Our Websites and Others 

We will disclose personal information when we believe in good faith that such disclosures (a) are required by law, including, for example, to comply with a court order or subpoena, or (b) will help to: enforce our Terms of Use; enforce contest, sweepstakes, promotions, and/or game rules; protect your safety or security, including the safety and security of property that belongs to you; and/or, protect the safety and security of our Websites or third parties.

top  
  
### Q4

| 

**What choices do you have about the collection, use, and sharing of your personally identifiable information?**  
  
---|---  
  
### A4

| 

As mentioned above, you have control over the personal information you submit to us. If at any time you decide to remove your personal information from our database, you may do so through our User Profile mechanism.

### Your California Privacy Rights

Since 2005, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits our customers who are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. For inquiries regarding our disclosure policy, please send us an e-mail to [privacy@gaspowered.com](mailto:privacy@gaspowered.com) or write us:

Gas Powered Games  
Attn.: Online Privacy  
5000 148th Ave NE Suite 200  
Redmond, WA 98052-5118

425-522-1600 

top  
  
### Q5

| 

**What kinds of security measures do we take to safeguard your personally identifiable information?**  
  
---|---  
  
### A5

| 

The security and confidentiality of your personal information is extremely important to us. We have implemented technical, administrative, and physical security measures to protect your personal information from unauthorized access and improper use. To prevent unauthorized electronic access to personal information, we maintain information collected online behind a firewall-protected server; use SSL encryption for purchases made through our online store; verify your identity by asking you for an email address or by other means; limit access to only those employees performing a legitimate business function; and keep back-ups offsite. From time to time, we review our security procedures to consider appropriate new technology and methods. However, please understand that, despite our best efforts, no security measure is perfect or impenetrable.

top  
  
### Q6

| 

**How can you update your personal information and profile?**  
  
---|---  
  
### A6

| 

You can access and update the contact information you gave us during registration (that is, your e-mail address or any other information that would directly enable us to contact you), by going to our profile section. Simply click on this link - <http://www.gaspowered.com/subscribe.php>. 

If you forget your password, read the instructions on the start page of the link above to help you recover it. If you need to recover your password, you can also contact us via e-mail at garage@gaspowered.com. Please include information in the e-mail that will help us identify your account so we can assist you with your request. We may also provide you an opportunity to update your contact information by sending you an e-mail or other communication that invites your response.

top  
  
### Q7

| 

**How can you ask questions, or send us comments, about this Privacy Policy?**  
  
---|---  
  
### A7

| 

If you have questions or wish to send us comments about this Privacy Policy, please send an e-mail with your questions or comments to [privacy@gaspowered.com](mailto:privacy@gaspowered.com) or write us:

Gas Powered Games  
Attn.: Online Privacy  
5000 148th Ave NE Suite 200  
Redmond, WA 98052-5118

425-522-1600 

Please be assured that any personal information that you provide in communications to the above email and postal mail addresses will not be used to send you promotional materials, unless you request it.

Gas Powered Games is a licensee of the ESRB's Privacy Online Program. If you believe that we have not responded to your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, please contact ESRB at <http://www.esrb.org/privacy/contact.jsp>

ESRB  
Attn.: Privacy Online Program  
317 Madison Avenue, 22nd Floor  
New York, NY 10017

privacy@esrb.org

top  
  
### Q8

| 

**How will you know if we amend this Privacy Policy?**  
  
---|---  
  
### A8

| 

We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time. If we make any material changes in the way we collect, use, or share your personal information, we will notify you by sending you an email at the last email address that you provided us, or by prominently posting notice of the changes on the Websites covered by this Privacy Policy. Any material changes to this Privacy Policy will be effective 30 days following our dispatch of an email notice to you or 30 days following our posting of notice of the changes on the Websites covered by this Privacy Policy.

Please note that, at all times, you are responsible for updating your personal information to provide us your current email address. If the last email address that you have provided us is not valid, or for any other reason is not capable of delivering to you the notice described above, our dispatch of the email containing such notice will nonetheless constitute effective notice of the changes described in the notice.

top
